8thwonder.ws 2008-06-16

# 8thwonder - Privacy Policy

8thwonder does not send Spam or sell email addresses. 

**About 8thwonder and the Information We Collect**

8thwonder is an online social networking community that connects people through networks of friends for dating or making new friends. To accomplish this, our users create their own profiles which are shown to the people in their personal network. A personal network consists of a user?s friends as well as the extended group of people that a user is connected to via chains of mutual friends. To fulfill the purpose of this site, some personal information we ask for is displayed to people within these personal networks.   
Information Collected/Tracked by 8thwonder   
Information submitted to 8thwonder 

8thwonder collects user-submitted account information such as name and email address to identify users and send notifications related to the use of the service. 8thwonder also collects user-submitted profile information such as gender, age, occupation, location, etc. 

**Information not Directly Submitted by Users to 8thwonder**

This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site. 

**Use of Information Obtained by 8thwonder**

Information users submit to 8thwonder 

Profile information as well as first name and photos are displayed to people in a user's personal network, to support the function of the site as social networking community where users can meet new people through their friends. Email address and full name are used when a user invites a friend via email to join the service, when a user requests to add another user to their friend list, and when we send notifications to a user related to their use of the service. Except when inviting or adding friends, a user's email address is not shared or displayed with people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on 8thwonder with each other through the 8thwonder service, without disclosing email addresses. We may also use a user's email address to send weekly updates or news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type by accessing their Account Info. 

**Information that users do not submit to us**

We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website.   
Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks 

Except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. 

**Links**

This site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that 8thwonder is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Cookies are used to manage sessions on our site.

Users must enable cookies to use our site. Also, users may optionally use a cookie to remember their password in order to automatically log in to our site. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user which they did not intentionally submit to us. 

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

8thwonder users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. 

**Invite a Friend**

If a user elects to use our Invite feature to invite a friend to our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. 8thwonder will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. 8thwonder stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondant to the friends list of the user sending the invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation. 8thwonder does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. The friend may contact 8thwonder to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Security**

Your 8thwonder account is password-protected. This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. We limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us. 

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our weekly updates or news may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email or by logging-in and changing their settings in the Account Info section of the site. 

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. 8thwonder does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by 8thwonder and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.   
Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
